The prophecy chose him to lead the last battle
The Veil is a action, adventure, science fiction
film directed by Brent Ryan Green.
Set in a war-torn land where tribal factions live in fear of annihilation, the film
tells the story of a deadly warrior leading a destructive war campaign.
When he is betrayed by his own and left for dead, he is healed by a mysterious princess and
taken in by a hidden tribe that believes he was chosen to wage a final battle.
Warrior, played by William Levy.
Aysel, played by William Moseley.
Zera, played by Serinda Swan.
Reiken, played by Nick E. Tarabay.
Warrior's Father, played by Adam Gregory.
Nikai, played by Brett DelBuono.
The Veil is a 2017 American post-apocalyptic film directed by Brent Ryan Green and
starring William Levy, Serinda Swan, William Moseley and Nick E.
The film is also known as Rise of a Warrior and Barbarian: Rise of the Warrior.
The film explores themes of princess, hero, moon, sword, emperor.
The tone is thought_provoking.